Guide to the Duke University Chapel Recordings, 1954-2002 UA.17.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Recordings, 1954-2002; 1
  - Clarence "Smoke" Kanipe - "Today", 1979 March 25; 1000
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1011)
  - Memorial Service for Jerome Huneycutt, Jr., 1979 March 31; 1001
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1012)
  - James C. Finlay - "Of Covenants and Careers", 1979 April 01; 1002
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1013)
  - Benjamin Chavis - Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Service, 1979 April 04; 1003
    - Tape 1 - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1014)
    - Tape 2 - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1015)
  - Edmund Steimle - "The Non-Hero", 1979 April 08; 1005
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1016)
  - Waldo Beach - Maundy Thursday Service, 1979 April 12; 1006
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1017)
  - Perry Miller - Good Friday Service, 1979 April 13; 1007
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1018)
  - Robert T. Young - "Christ Appeared...Also to Me" Easter Service 9:00 am, 1979 April 15; 1008
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1019)
  - Robert T. Young - "Christ Appeared...Also to Me" Easter Service 11:00 am, 1979 April 15; 1009
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1020)
  - Herbert O. Edwards - "When Experience Outruns Theology", 1979 April 22; 1010
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1021)
  - Robert T. Young - "I John...Share with You", 1979 April 29; 1011
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1022)
  - Krister Stendahl - "To Serve, to Succeed, and to Survive" Baccalaureate Service, 1979 May 05; 1012
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1023)
  - John W. Vannorsdall - "Figments of Our Imagination" Baccalaureate Service 9:00 am, 1979 May 06; 1013
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1024)
  - John W. Vannorsdall - "Figments of Our Imagination" Baccalaureate Service 11:00 am, 1979 May 06; 1014
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1025)
  - Helen G. Crotwell - "Live Boldly", 1979 May 13; 1015
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1026)
  - John K. Bergland - "In This Is Love—1 John 4:10", 1979 May 20; 1016
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1027)
  - Paul A. Mickey - "A Little Horn of Plenty", 1979 May 27; 1017
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1028)
  - Charles K. Robinson - "Does God Suffer, Too?", 1979 June 03; 1018
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1029)
  - Vergel L. Lattimore, III - "Crisis, Change, and a Chance…to Be Made New", 1979 June 10; 1019
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1030)
  - Diane Kenney - "Running the Race with Assurance", 1979 June 17; 1020
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1031)
  - Albert F. Fisher - "Midway the Highway of Life", 1979 June 24; 1021
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1032)
  - Hugh Anderson - "A Banner with a Strange Device", 1979 July 01; 1022
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1034)
  - Lawrence E. Johnson - "A Vision of God, Self, and Service", 1979 July 08; 1023
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0006)
  - Eugene Owens - "The Dis-Ease of Emptiness", 1979 July 15; 1024
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1035)
  - Phillis L. Scott - "God's Dishonorable Prophets", 1979 July 22; 1025
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1036)
  - Richard J. Crowder - "On Making the Best of a Raw Deal", 1979 August 05
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1038)
  - Juanita Wright - "Encounters with the Lord", 1979 July 29; 1026
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1037)
  - Charles E. Shannon - "Here's Something to Believe In", 1979 August 12; 1027
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1178)
  - Joseph B. Bethea - "The Gospel of Reconciliation", 1979 August 19; 1028
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1039)
  - James Bailey - "The Power to Be Healed", 1979 August 26; 1029
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1040)
  - Robert T. Young - "I am the Alpha and the Omega", 1979 September 02; 1030
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1041)
    - Copy - audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0007)
  - Memorial Service for Kenneth Willis Clark, 1979 September 05; 1031
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1042)
  - William S. Coffin - "Three Questions", 1979 September 09; 1032
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1043)
  - Robert T. Young - "Who Wants a Messiah like This?!", 1979 September 16; 1033
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 27, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1033)
  - William H. Willimon - "The Last and the Least", 1979 September 23; 1034
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1044)
  - Robert T. Young - "The Touch of the Healing God", 1979 September 30; 1035
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1045)
  - C. Eric Lincoln - "The Beauty of Being One", 1979 October 07; 1036
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1046)
  - Memorial Service for Bruce Shepherd, 1979 October 12; 1037
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1047)
  - Robert T. Young - "Is Christ Divided?", 1979 October 14; 1038
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1048)
  - Leander Keck - "Seeing and Not Seeing", 1979 October 21; 1039
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1049)
  - Robert T. Young - "Love…Is for Us", 1979 October 28; 1040
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1050)
  - Robert T. Young - "Behold, I Make All Things New", 1979 November 04; 1041
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1051)
  - John Carlton - "The Fire and the Calf", 1979 November 11; 1042
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1052)
  - Edwin M. Richardson - "We Need More Bat Boys!", 1979 November 18; 1043
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1053)
  - Robert T. Young - Thanksgiving Service, 1979 November 22; 1044
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1054)
  - Robert T. Young - "His Kingdom...Shall Not Be Destroyed", 1979 November 25; 1045
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1055)
  - Thomas A. Langford - "The Slaughter of the Innocents", 1979 December 02; 1046
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1056)
  - Wilson O. Weldon - "Dangerous Legacies", 1979 December 09; 1047
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1057)
  - Memorial Service for Mark Scholl, 1979 December 12; 1048
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1058)
  - Robert T. Young - "Rejoice in the Lord Always", 1979 December 16; 1049
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1059)
  - Robert T. Young - "Christmas, A. D. 1980", 1979 December 23; 1050
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1060)
  - Christmas Eve Service, 1979 December 24; 1051
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1061)
  - Memorial Service for James H. Phillips, 1979 December 26; 1052
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1062)
  - Juanita B. Wright - "And the Word Was Made Flesh", 1979 December 30; 1053
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1063)
  - Memorial Service for Pearl Wells Alden, 1980 January 02; 1054
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1064)
  - James M. Efird - "Brains, Heart, and Courage", 1980 January 06; 1055
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1065)
  - Robert T. Young - "Holy Moments", 1980 January 13; 1056
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1066)
  - Memorial Service for George B. Ehlhardt, 1980 January 13; 1057
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 28, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1067)
  - Memorial Service for Charles E. Fox, 1980 January 17; 1058
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1068)
  - John K. Bergland - "When the Wine Fails", 1980 January 20; 1059
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1069)
  - Gardner Taylor - "On Remembering Who We Are", 1980 January 27; 1060
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1070)
  - S. Collins Kilburn - "What's Next in Ecumenism?" Service of Christian Unity, 1980 January 27; 1061
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1071)
  - Michael Novak - "The Experience of Nothingness", 1980 February 03; 1062
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1072)
  - Robert T. Young - "Encounter with the Lord God Almighty", 1980 February 10; 1063
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1073)
  - Fleming Rutledge - "Was Blind but Now I See", 1980 February 17; 1064
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1074)
  - Richard Lischer - "Wilderness Journey", 1980 February 24; 1065
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1075)
  - Memorial Service for Michael Lee Visscher, 1980 February 28; 1066
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1076)
  - Paul Moore, Jr. - "The Open Church", 1980 March 02; 1067
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1077)
  - Robert T. Young - "Is It Persistence That Pays Off?", 1980 March 09; 1068
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1078)
  - Robert W. Estill - Ordination and Consecration, 1980 March 15; 1069
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1079)
  - Juanita Bass Wright - "God's Forgiveness", 1980 March 16; 1070
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1080)
  - Memorial Service for Joseph Banks Rhine, 1980 March 22; 1071
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1081)
  - Amanda Lee Berry - "Encouragement in Christ for a Loving Community", 1980 March 23; 1072
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1082)
  - A. James Armstrong - "King of Kings? Ha!...", 1980 March 30; 1073
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1083)
  - Juanita Bass Wright - "Serve the People", 1980 April 03; 1074
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1084)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Service, 1980 April 04; 1075
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1085)
  - Robert T. Young - "Why Do You Seek the Living among the Dead?", 1980 April 06; 1076
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1086)
  - Juanita Bass Wright - "No Compromise", 1980 April 13; 1077
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1087)
  - Harrell F. Beck - "The Story of the Three Wise Women", 1980 April 20; 1078
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1088)
  - B. Maurice Ritchie - "Salvation Belongs to Our God", 1980 April 27; 1079
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1089)
  - Robert T. Young - "You Have Forsaken Your First Love", 1980 May 04; 1080
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1090)
  - W. Kenneth Goodson - "Eruditio et Religio" Baccalaureate Service, 1980 May 11; 1081
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1091)
  - Juanita Bass Wright - "Free to Leave", 1980 May 18; 1082
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1092)
  - Memorial Service for Frank Traver deVyver, 1980 May 21; 1083
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1093)
  - Robert T. Young - "Power to Become", 1980 May 25; 1084
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1094)
  - Dennis M. Campbell - "Joy Unmeasured", 1980 June 01; 1085
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1095)
  - Memorial Service for Deryl Hort, 1980 June 03; 1086
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1096)
  - Wedding of Sharron Slaughter and William Stokes, 1980 June 07; 1087
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1097)
  - Peter James Lee - "The Difference Faith Makes", 1980 June 08; 1088
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1098)
  - Thomas B. Stockton - "Values Vertigo", 1980 June 15; 1089
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1099)
  - L. Bevel Jones - "When Faith Falls Short", 1980 June 22; 1090
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1100)
  - J. Davison Philips - "To Behold and to Inquire", 1980 June 29; 1091
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1101)
  - Charlene P. Kammerer - "In Search of Living Water", 1980 July 06; 1092
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1102)
  - Robert T. Young - "The Recovery of the Lost", 1980 July 13; 1093
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 29, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1103)
  - Joseph L. Gipson - "Question of Accountability", 1980 July 20; 1094
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1104)
  - F. Belton Joyner, Jr. - "What Does This Laughter Mean?", 1980 July 27; 1095
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1105)
  - Lawrence E. Johnson - "Earthly Gods", 1980 August 03; 1096
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1106)
  - Ellen Kirby - "Going against the Grain: Consider the Ravens", 1980 August 10; 1097
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1107)
  - Charlene P. Kammerer - "On Your Mark", 1980 August 17; 1098
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1108)
  - James W. Ferree - "What Is the Goal of Life?", 1980 August 24; 1099
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1109)
  - Robert T. Young - "The Glory of the Now", 1980 August 31; 1100
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1110)
  - Robert T. Young - "A New Covenant Is Risky Indeed", 1980 September 07; 1101
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1111)
  - Andrew Young - Sermon Untitled, 1980 September 14; 1102
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1112)
  - Charlene Kammerer - "Claiming Your Call", 1980 September 21; 1103
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1113)
  - Robert T. Young - "For the Living of These Days", 1980 September 28; 1104
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1114)
  - Richard Lischer - "Redeem the Time", 1980 October 12; 1105
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1115)
  - Robert E. Cushman - "For the Relief of Man's Estate: Lovely Is Thy Dwelling Place, O Lord of Hosts" 50th Anniversary Chapel Service, 1980 October 19; 1106
    - Tape 1 - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1116)
    - Tape 2 - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1117)
    - Copy - audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0008)
  - Robert T. Young - "From Illusion to Prayer", 1980 October 26; 1107
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1118)
  - Robert T. Young - "You Will Find Rest for Your Souls", 1980 November 02; 1108
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1119)
  - Stuart C. Henry - "Moment of Truth", 1980 November 09; 1109
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1120)
  - John T. Walker - "Reconciliation", 1980 November 16; 1110
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1121)
  - Memorial Service for Tracy Bridges, 1980 November 19; 1111
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1122)
  - Charlene P. Kammerer - "Lest We Forget", 1980 November 23; 1112
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1123)
  - Robert T. Young - "The Night Is Far Gone, the Day Is at Hand", 1980 November 30; 1113
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1124)
  - Elizabeth Achtemeier - "Romanticism, Reality, and the Christmas Child", 1980 December 07; 1114
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1125)
  - Joel D. McDavid - "Never Off Duty", 1980 December 14; 1115
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1126)
  - Robert T. Young - "Just a Simple Story", 1980 December 21; 1116
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1127)
  - Christmas Eve Service, 1980 December 25; 1117
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1128)
  - Charlene P. Kammerer - "Come and See", 1980 December 28; 1118
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1129)
  - Fred Herzog - "The Idea of the University", 1981 January 03; 1119
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0009)
  - Thomas C. Davis - "The Cosmic Christ", 1981 January 04; 1120
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1130)
  - Memorial Service for Herman O. Hartley, 1981 January 05; 1121
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1131)
  - Richard Lischer - "The Sign Interprets Us", 1981 January 10; 1122
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0010)
  - Robert T. Young - "Surprised by Grace", 1981 January 11; 1123
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1132)
  - Memorial Service for Harry Levy, 1981 January 14; 1124
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1133)
  - John Killinger - "Discovering the Joy of Your Limitations", 1981 January 18; 1125
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1134)
  - C. Eric Lincoln; Charles Petty; A. Kenneth Pye - "Message" Service of Thanksgiving for the Release of Hostages in Iran, 1981 January 21; 1126
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1135)
  - Robert T. Young - "For God so Loved the World", 1981 January 25; 1127
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1136)
  - W. Kenneth Goodson - "Unchanging Realities in a Changing World", 1981 February 01; 1128
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1137)
  - Robert T. Young - "You Proclaim the Lord's Death", 1981 February 08; 1129
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1138)
  - Memorial Service for Anne Curtis Cole, 1981 February 11; 1130
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 30, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1139)
  - John K. Bergland - "Beneath the Law, but beyond the Laws", 1981 February 15; 1131
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1140)
  - Charlene P. Kammerer - "Walking through the Valley of the Shadow", 1981 February 22; 1132
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1141)
  - Scott Klinger - "Where Is the Peace of Christ?", 1981 March 01; 1133
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1142)
  - Memorial Service for Dorothy Stambaugh Westafer, 1981 March 08; 1134
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1143)
  - Robert T. Young - "If...", 1981 March 08; 1135
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1144)
  - D. Moody Smith - "The Woman of Samaria", 1981 March 15; 1136
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1145)
  - Joseph H. Jackson - "Life's Most Dreadful Famine", 1981 March 22; 1137
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1146)
  - Robert T. Young - "The Poor You Have with You Always", 1981 March 29; 1138
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1147)
  - Virginia R. Mollenkott - "Sickness, Self-Righteousness, and Healing", 1981 April 05; 1139
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1148)
  - Peggy Way - "Happy Endings", 1981 April 12; 1140
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1149)
  - Service of Concern for Atlanta's Children, 1981 April 13; 1141
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1150)
  - Robert T. Young - Maundy Thursday Service, 1981 April 16; 1142
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1151)
  - Good Friday Service, 1981 April 17; 1143
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1152)
  - Robert T. Young - "What Does It Mean to Say 'He Has Risen'", 1981 April 19; 1144
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 31, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1153)
  - Charlene P. Kammerer - "Post-Resurrection Depression", 1981 April 26; 1145